Hello, and welcome to the complete JavaScript course.
大家好，欢迎到JavaScript完整教程来。
I'm really excited to have you in this massive course.
我真的很高兴，你们能加入到这个庞大的系列教程中来。
And I promise, you made the right choice
我保证，你们的选择是对的
by joining me in this adventure.
加入到我的冒险之旅吧.
Because today, JavaScript is not only
因为在现在，JavaScript不仅仅
the most popular programming language in the world,
是世界上最流行的语言（作者有点拼啊）,
but it also powers the entire modern internet.
但他也为整个互联网技术提供支持（全栈的最佳语言）。
Now without further ado, I wanna give you a quick overview
废话不多说，我来给你们快速介绍一下
of how this course is organized,
这个教程是如何组织安排的
the projects that we're gonna code together,
我们会一起编程的项目是什么（敲代码）
and also, what exactly you're gonna learn in this course.
而且，在课程里我们会学到什么.
So, the course contains a total of eight sections
课程包括8个章节
with over 26 hours of content.
26小时的授课内容
So we're gonna kick off the course in section two
因此，我们会从第二部分
with the very basics of the JavaScript language,
学习JavaScript语言的基础
and programming in general, to give you a solid foundation
和编程的基础知识, 为课程的其余部分
for the rest of the course.
提供坚实的基础（打好基础啊）.
After that, we're gonna take a look behind the scenes
在那之后，我们会看看JavaScript的底层知识
of JavaScript and learn how the language actually works.
并了解语言实际上是如何工作的
And this is gonna be a good mix
这将是理论和实践
of theory and practical lectures,
的完美结合,
designed to give you the knowledge
这样来可以为您提供许多
that many other JavaScript beginners simply don't have.
JavaScript初学者根本没有的知识。
We then move on to our first project,
然后就会继续开始我们的第一个项目,
where we use JavaScript in the browser
我们会在这个项目中使用JavaScript
for the very first time.
这可是第一次在游览器中使用啊（废话真多）。
And so we're gonna code up this really cool game
我们会编写一个非常酷的游戏
where we make JavaScript actually interact
这里会让JavaScript
with an HTML webpage.
与HTML页面交互.
Alright, and after that, we're gonna take a deep dive
在那之后，我们会深入研究
into the most advanced JavaScript concepts,
最先进的JavaScript概念,
and that's objects and functions.
以及他们的对象和功能。
We're gonna talk about things like prototypal inheritance,
我们会讨论一些比如原型继承（prototypal inheritance）,
first-class functions, closures, and a lot more stuff.
一级类方法，闭包和更多的东西。
Next up, we put everything we learned
接下来，我们将我们学到的内容
up until this point together,
整合到一起,
and code this beautiful budget app,
编写一个美丽的预算应用,
where you can track incomes and expenses
可以跟踪预算和支出
and calculate the global budget for any given month.
并可以计算任何一个月的费用。
So in this project, you're gonna learn tons of new stuff
因此在这个项目里，你将学习大量新的内容
like how to structure and organize your code
例如如何构建和组织代码
and how to actually think about problems and solutions.
如何考虑实际问题和解决方案。
Then, starting from section number seven,
然后，在第七部分开始
we're gonna start using next generation JavaScript.
我们将开始使用下一代JavaScript
So ES6, ES7, and even some ES8 features.
比如ES6, ES7, 甚至包括 ES8 特性.
So we're gonna start by looking at what's new in ES6,
所以我们首先要看看ES6,
or ES2015, and then code some examples with the new syntax.
或ES2015中的新特性，然后使用新语法编写一些示例
Next up, you're gonna learn
接下来，你将学习
all about asynchronous JavaScript, which is used for things
关于js异步的知识，他用于
like loading data from external servers with AJAX.
比如通过AJAX加载外部服务的数据。
And then finally, to wrap up the course,
最后结束课程时
this is the biggest project,
会建立一个庞大的项目,
coded entirely in ES6, ES7, and even ES8.
完全用ES6, ES7, 甚至 ES8来编写。
So we're fetching data from a real API here
我们会获取真实的api数据，
and building this real-world app around it
使用最新的技术
using the latest technologies,
构建一个现实版的应用
and also tools like NPM, Babel, and Webpack.
这里面会用到NPM，Babel，Webpack等工具.
Now, in all of the videos, I always explain
现在，在所有视频中，我会经常
every single detail of the JavaScript language
解释js的所有使用细节
or of the technique that I'm using.
或者说是所有使用到的技术。
But sometimes, you may still have a question
但是，某些时候你还是有
about one of the topics that you're learning
学习中碰到的疑问
in a particular video, or maybe you just run into a problem
或者是代码运行时产生的错误
with your code and need help fixing it.
你需要我帮组你来解决它。
Well, either way, you can always get help here
在这里，你可以得到许多帮组
in the Udemy Q and A section.
比如在下面留言
So, at the bottom of the video that you're watching,
这样，你就会在视频
you will always find the questions section
下面发现类似的问题
for that specific video.
相应的视频会对应相应的问题
So whenever you have a question,
所以,一旦你有问题了
you can check if another student
你可以检查一下是不是其他同学
has already asked the same question before,
已经问过相同的问题了
and if not, well, you can just post your own.
如果没有，那你就可以提交你自己的问题
And you will then get friendly and fast support
你会得到友善的回答
from me or from my team
这些回答来自个人也来自团队。
so that you're back to writing code as fast as possible.
这样你就能尽可能快的编程。
So I hope you're gonna have a ton of fun with the course,
我希望你能在这个课程学的开心,
that you become a real advanced JavaScript developer,
成为一个真正的JavaScript开发者,
and that you will take your web development career
得到自己满意的工作
to the next level.
更好一点可以去阿里，腾讯试试。
That's really all I want to achieve with this course.
这些都是我想要的。
And with that being said, let's finally get started.
说完了，我们开始吧。